<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on David Gardiner Profile</title>
    <link>https://davidmarkgardiner.com/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on David Gardiner Profile</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 10:34:38 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidmarkgardiner.com/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pod Secutiry Admission</title>
      <link>https://davidmarkgardiner.com/blogs/pod-secutiry-admission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 10:34:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmarkgardiner.com/blogs/pod-secutiry-admission/</guid>
      <description>Pod Security Admission pod-security-admission
pod-security-standards
migrate-from-psp
Pod Security Admission has replaced Pod Security Policy (PSP) PSA implements the Pod Security Standards (PSS), a set of policies describing various security-related characteristics of workloads in a Kubernetes cluster. As of version 1.25, PSA is now a stable feature, and PSP has been completely removed.
Pod Security Admission The Kubernetes Pod Security Standards define different isolation levels for Pods. These standards allow you to clearly and consistently define how to restrict the behavior of Pods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pod Security Standards</title>
      <link>https://davidmarkgardiner.com/blogs/pod-security-standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 10:27:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmarkgardiner.com/blogs/pod-security-standards/</guid>
      <description>pod-security-admission
pod-security-standards
migrate-from-psp
Pod Security Standards The Kubernetes Pod Security Standards define different isolation levels for Pods. These standards let you define how you want to restrict the behavior of pods in a clear, consistent fashion.
Kubernetes offers a built-in Pod Security admission controller to enforce the Pod Security Standards. Pod security restrictions are applied at the namespace level when pods are created.
# Privileged Unrestricted policy, providing the widest possible level of permissions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
